I want to be like her someday.
You're always so amazing, Chidorigafuchi.
I'm tired of trite compliments
like "amazing."
Of course, with your intellect,
I'm sure it's the best you're capable of.
Well, excuse me.
And I was only up against a dummy Magitech
built by the Engineering Division.
Of course I'd be able to do that.
Well, excuse us!
After all, I'm here to fight.
Cut them apart! Blade!
Fire!
Himekawa's the best!
Yurishia-sama!
The destructive powers of Neros and Kuros
are on a whole other level, aren't they?
We need to develop weapons
that are as good as Amaterasu's!
Chidorigafuchi?
Episode Three
Gentle Days - Memories
So that data was accurate after all.
After Aine, Yurishia has succeeded
in her Heart Hybrid, too.
Now we can proceed as planned.
But...
The genius scientist,
Dr. Nayuta Hida, developed
our strongest weapons and the only ones
that can take on Magitechs:
the Heart Hybrid Gears.
But...
Great power always comes
at an even greater price, huh?
I wonder what expression she's
got on her face now, that woman.
Kizuna!
Y-Yurishia?
So, what did you think of my exploits
during the training exercise?
You fell in love a little, didn't you?
U-Um...
No wonder you're the American ace.
I was impressed. Really.
Do you really mean that?
Then give me a reward.
Wow! Fantastic!
Why did you want to go to the
Kyoto float for your reward?
Because I've always wanted to
have a chance to go sightseeing.
Hey, Kizuna,
is this temple the real deal?
It's a replica.
There wasn't enough time to get all our
cultural assets aboard the megafloats.
I see.
I want to see the real one someday.
You can.
Once we all go back to Japan.
That's why we're fighting.
Okay, Kizuna.
Let's go to the next one!
Next?
I didn't expect to spend the day
touring the megafloat.
It's not that big,
but it feels like we've
traveled all over Japan.
Sorry for dragging you along.
But it was so much fun!
You're really proactive, Yurishia.
Not many people would act on a crazy idea
like this, even if they did think of it.
You're right.
I think I've changed.
Changed?
When we were attacked by that
Magitech weapon on that uninhabited island,
I thought I might die,
for the first time in my life.
But when you saved me, this is what I felt:
I want to live my life more.
Yurishia.
I want to have more fun.
I want to do more things,
like fall in love with a boy.
No, I...
It's thanks to you that I can feel this way.
Thank you.
I don't mind her saying thanks,
but I don't know about this...
Hey, is that you, Himekawa?
Hida-kun?
Do you always stay at school this late?
The disciplinary committee sure has it rough.
There's no end of students causing problems.
Especially lewd boys.
But I like this school.
I want to make the lives of my
fellow students as fun as possible.
That is my desire,
as well as my duty.
You're really dedicated, huh?
I like that.
L-Like?
Wh-What are you saying?
That's indecent!
Himekawa...
H-Hida-kun...
A Heart Hybrid?
In an instant?
Why?
How could I be so perverted?
Chidorigafuchi?
Aine-san's always like that.
She always trains by herself.
I wanted to spar with her,
so I went up to talk to her,
but she ignored me.
At this point, everyone keeps
their distance from her.
She has a strange obsession with fighting.
Yurishia-san and I don't know
what she's thinking, either.
Even though we're all part of Amaterasu.
After all, I'm here to fight.
So he managed to Hybrid Heart
with Himekawa, too?
Guess I can't run away now.
Chidorigafuchi-san?
She only came here in high school,
so I don't know the details.
Come to think of it,
I've never seen her smile.
I see...
U-Um...
Can I go?
Y-Yeah...
What's this about me?
Well, this sucks.
This is my chance to learn
about Chidorigafuchi,
but what do I say?
Hey.
Have you eaten yet?
No, not yet.
I see.
Then I'll give you this.
Be grateful.
Th-That looks good.
Are these handmade?
Yes.
I bought them at a convenience store,
cut them in half,
and put them in a lunchbox.
I don't think that qualifies as handmade.
I see.
Then what is the definition of handmade?
Huh?
How strict is the definition?
If I can't use something
that's already made,
I'd have to grow the wheat
for the bread myself, right?
Oh, I'd have to go catch the tuna, too.
I'll be right back. Can you wait here?
I'm sorry!
I appreciate it very much!
As long as you understand.
What am I doing here again?
Thank you.
Wait.
There's one other thing I want you to eat.
Dessert or something?
H-Hey, you can't mean—?!
What are you doing?
We're in broad daylight!
I read in one of those books that
if you do it in a place like this,
the immorality of it
turns the guy on more.
What kind of book did you read?
I-It doesn't matter!
Come, Hybrid Heart with me right now!
Are you...?
Wh-What are you talking about,
you inferior life form?
Do you think that I, of all people,
would be scared of something like this?
But you're shaking.
I'm about to get my Immoral Weapon.
I'm so happy, I'm shaking.
Immoral Weapon?
What's that... Wait!
Is this still not good enough?
Why am I getting excited?
I bet she's wearing a pilot suit
underneath like before—
Or not!
Go ahead. You can touch them.
But...
Hurry up.
W-Wait!
They're so soft...
Th-This is weird!
You can't force it...
And you have to think about
how the other person feels.
I don't care.
I can't lose.
I can't let Yurishia and Hayuru
beat me forever.
You...
I want power.
And for that...
I don't care what happens to me!
Fine.
Hey,
we're doing a Heart Hybrid, right?
I can't do it.
Not when you've got that look on your face.
You don't know anything about me, right?
And I don't know anything about you.
So we need to take more time
to learn about each other.
That's impossible.
Impossible?
H-Hey!
Sis?
Hello?
Kizuna, it's Reiri.
I need to talk to you.
Can we meet?
Y-Yeah.
Here.
Do you remember this room, Kizuna?
Yeah.
I could never forget it.
This is...
This is the place...
...where it all began.
I underwent the Core Install surgery
for the Heart Hybrid Gear.
Right here.
I was scared.
But I did it for Mom.
I wanted Mom's approval,
so I helped with the Gear experiment.
But Mom...
I'll never forget.
That's right.
Kizuna, actually...
That aside, there was something
I wanted to ask you.
Ask me?
I want you to tell me what
you know about Chidorigafuchi.
Aine?
Why?
Because I have to know about her, I think.
What she's like, where she came from,
why she's here...
I want to know.
There are no records of her earlier life.
Seven years ago, in Chidorigafuchi, Tokyo,
a girl with no known identity was found.
She had no memories
and didn't remember her name or identity.
Was that...?
Yes, that was Aine.
During the physical exam she took
as part of the efforts to identify her,
it was found that she had very
high compatibility with the Gears.
So the lab took her in,
as an experimental subject for that woman.
Hello, Aine Chidorigafuchi-san.
Aine...
Then...
Aine Chidorigafuchi is the name
that woman gave her.
After she took her in,
her life at the lab began.
All she ever did was
take part in experiments.
But they suddenly came to an end
when Nayuta Hida disappeared.
That woman disappeared one day,
and we still don't know why.
Or, of course, where she went.
That's all I know.
I see.
She's...
She's always been alone, huh?
It might take time, but I'm sure
we can understand each other.
Sorry, but our time is limited.
What do you mean?
The archive you're about to see
was only recently discovered.
No one but Reiri and I know about it.
Be careful.
It will link with your vision.
Linkage.
It hurts...
I can't take any more....
Continue, please.
But my Hybrid Count...
All right.
We'll take control of
the Gear from here, then.
Dr. N-Nayuta.
No... Doctor... stop!
Output increasing.
Someone, stop!
Count has entered the danger zone.
Stop it! No! I don't want to die!
Subject's vitals are yellow.
Count remaining: 7, 6, 5, 4,
I'm going to die!
No!
3, 2, 1.
Count zero.
Vitals lost.
Increasing maximum output value by 5.0.
Thank you.
This was good data.
What was that?
As you just saw,
the Hybrid Count is the energy
source of the Hybrid Gear.
At the same time, it is the
life energy of the pilot.
With the Eros, Zeros, Neros, and Kuros,
all entries in the Ros series,
if their count drops to zero...
The pilot dies.
No one knows this.
Not even the members of Amaterasu.
But, Kizuna,
as the unit commander,
I wanted you to know.
You're kidding.
Then everyone...
had those cores installed
without knowing anything,
and they're risking their
lives each time they fight?
You knew that, and you
made them fight anyway?!
This fact only came to light very recently.
And do you think Reiri didn't suffer
when she found out?
Then that's just another reason
to find another way!
We don't...
We don't have a choice.
This is all we have to fight the enemy.
So what do I do?
I have to order them to fight, right?
Sis...
That is my responsibility.
I'm going to hell for this, I'm sure.
But even so...
You're our one hope, Kizuna.
The Heart Hybrid...
You're the only one who can save their lives.
That is the special feature of Eros,
the Gear that was installed in you, a boy.
I'm the only one who can save them?
Welcome back, Captain!
Sylvia...
Did you make all this?
Yes!
It's my job to take care of you, Captain!
I see.
It looks good.
But are you okay?
You look tired.
No, that's not true.
I see.
If you need anything, let me know.
I want to help you!
Thanks, Sylvia.
Captain, huh?
An enemy fleet has appeared!
Illustration: Keita Hagio
I want my Immoral Weapon.
Because fighting is the only reason
I'm allowed to be here.
That's not true!
Tell me who you really are, Aine.
Next time: Climax Hybrid
D-Don't call me by my first name...
Dummy.